(Leonard:)-We should call her.
-Yeah.
(Penny:)Amy, it's Penny. Hey.
Just a little heads-up.
(Penny:)Leonard bought a dining room table.
(Penny:)Yeah. Sheldon's breaking up with you.
Amy? Amy?
(Sheldon:)Amy?
(Sheldon:)I'll get right to the point.
(Sheldon:)I think we need to end this
relationship, so....
(Sheldon:)Just sign this
with your finger, and...
(Sheldon:)Please don't cry on my iPad.
I didn't get AppleCare.
(Amy:)I'm not surprised you want
to end the relationship.
(Amy:)I'm a little surprised
you didn't get AppleCare.
(Amy:)Anyway, enjoy your life.
Where do I sign?
(Sheldon:)At the bottom. I must say,
(Sheldon:)I'm relieved you're not making
more of a scene out of this.
(Amy:)I've already moved on.
(Amy:)Besides, this breakup has
nothing to do with me.
(Sheldon:)It doesn't?
(Amy:)Of course not.
This is just Leonard
(Amy:)trying to take the focus
off that dreadful table